[{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983527509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7148,"timeElapsed":42065},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983532214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4704,"timeElapsed":46771},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983536695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4478,"timeElapsed":51252},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983539948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3252,"timeElapsed":54505},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983542746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2797,"timeElapsed":57303},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983548993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6244,"timeElapsed":63550},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983553236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4238,"timeElapsed":67793},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983557636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4395,"timeElapsed":72193},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983561778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"35","question":"What makes you most angry?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4138,"timeElapsed":76335},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983568096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4687,"timeElapsed":82653},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983571084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2985,"timeElapsed":85641},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983574354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3266,"timeElapsed":88911},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983576974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2618,"timeElapsed":91531},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983579455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2477,"timeElapsed":94012},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983584208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4750,"timeElapsed":98765},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983587443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":3231,"timeElapsed":101999},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983591049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":3603,"timeElapsed":105606},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983594547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":3495,"timeElapsed":109104},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983602008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":5895,"timeElapsed":116565},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983605479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3467,"timeElapsed":120036},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983612387,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6904,"timeElapsed":126944},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983616603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4212,"timeElapsed":131160},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983618983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2376,"timeElapsed":133540},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983621593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2607,"timeElapsed":136150},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983626173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":4576,"timeElapsed":140730},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983630015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3838,"timeElapsed":144572},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983634570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4551,"timeElapsed":149127},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983637077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2503,"timeElapsed":151634},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983646273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7411,"timeElapsed":160829},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983651043,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4767,"timeElapsed":165600},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983656068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":5022,"timeElapsed":170625},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983659366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3295,"timeElapsed":173923},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983663756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":4386,"timeElapsed":178313},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983667364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3604,"timeElapsed":181921},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983673435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6068,"timeElapsed":187992},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983676615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3176,"timeElapsed":191172},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983679268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2649,"timeElapsed":193825},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983681776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2504,"timeElapsed":196333},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983687881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4939,"timeElapsed":202438},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983690416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2531,"timeElapsed":204973},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983692896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2476,"timeElapsed":207453},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983695431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2531,"timeElapsed":209988},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983698746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3311,"timeElapsed":213302},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983702290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3541,"timeElapsed":216847},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983704717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2423,"timeElapsed":219274},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983707678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2958,"timeElapsed":222235},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983709859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2177,"timeElapsed":224416},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983719798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":8346,"timeElapsed":234355},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983722996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3194,"timeElapsed":237553},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983726519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3520,"timeElapsed":241076},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983731798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5275,"timeElapsed":246355},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983736442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4641,"timeElapsed":250999},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983741241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4795,"timeElapsed":255797},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983745027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3783,"timeElapsed":259584},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983748125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3094,"timeElapsed":262682},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983750434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"207","question":"Is your current home rented or owned by you? If rented, are you hoping to one day own a home? If owned, how long have you owned it for?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2305,"timeElapsed":264991},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983777537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":25744,"timeElapsed":292094},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983779881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2340,"timeElapsed":294437},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983783816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3933,"timeElapsed":298373},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983786824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2995,"timeElapsed":301381},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983789801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2973,"timeElapsed":304358},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983793219,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3414,"timeElapsed":307775},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983795571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2349,"timeElapsed":310128},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983799385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3810,"timeElapsed":313942},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983801729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2340,"timeElapsed":316286},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983811623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":8637,"timeElapsed":326180},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983814668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3041,"timeElapsed":329225},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983817320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2648,"timeElapsed":331877},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983819328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2005,"timeElapsed":333885},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983821861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2530,"timeElapsed":336418},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983825669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3804,"timeElapsed":340226},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983828930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3257,"timeElapsed":343487},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983832074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3140,"timeElapsed":346631},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983834174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2097,"timeElapsed":348731},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983843087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7566,"timeElapsed":357644},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983845366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2275,"timeElapsed":359923},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983847858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2488,"timeElapsed":362415},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983850454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2593,"timeElapsed":365011},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983852782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2324,"timeElapsed":367339},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983856744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3959,"timeElapsed":371301},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983859304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2557,"timeElapsed":373861},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983862394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3086,"timeElapsed":376951},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983865191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2793,"timeElapsed":379748},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983871205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4539,"timeElapsed":385762},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983873125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1917,"timeElapsed":387682},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983875686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2558,"timeElapsed":390243},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983877885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2195,"timeElapsed":392442},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983880663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2774,"timeElapsed":395220},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983883217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2550,"timeElapsed":397774},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983885353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2133,"timeElapsed":399910},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983889022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3665,"timeElapsed":403578},{"subjectID":"sks3wvjpga","prolificID":"5b5f23420085cb0001872849","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769bf099ce3c03f47ebbdff","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734983891212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"85","question":"Name one of your core beliefs and describe why it is important to you.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2187,"timeElapsed":405769}]